Guide to the Alfred Stieglitz / Georgia O'Keeffe Archive
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Alfred Stieglitz: Documentary Ephemera, 1728-1980; Series III; 17.35; (19 boxes)
  - SCRAPBOOKS
    The books overlap in date and subject matter, and are arranged in no discernable order with the exception of volumes seven and eight, which are devoted to documenting musical and theatrical performances Stieglitz attended. Reference photocopies of all letters in the books were made and interfiled into the correspondence files (Series I).
    See Appendix One of this finding aid for an expanded description of the scrapbooks' contents, and Appendix Five to determine which microfilm reels include the scrapbooks. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Scrapbook Number 1, 1900-12, n.d. (Box 102)
      Contains material concerning the Photo-Secession and the "291" Gallery.
    - Scrapbook Number 2, 1902-11 (Box 103)
      Contains material concerning Camera Work and the "291" Gallery.
    - Scrapbook Number 3, 1902-13, n.d. (Box 104)
      Contains material concerning the Photo-Secession exhibitions.
      Conditions Governing Access
      Restricted fragile material. Microfilm is available. See Appendix Five for requesting microfilm. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Scrapbook Number 4, 1896-1907 (Box 105)
      Contains material concerning the Photo-Secession and exhibitions.
    - Scrapbook Number 5, 1897-1916, n.d. (Box 106)
      Contains articles by and about Stieglitz, and reviews of Photo-Secession and "291" Gallery exhibitions.
    - Scrapbook Number 6, 1887-1909, n.d. (Box 107)
      Contains articles by and about Stieglitz, catalogues and reviews of Photo-Secession exhibitions, and reproductions of Stieglitz photographs.
    - Scrapbook Number 7, 1877-88
      Contains cast lists cut from programs of opera and theater performances attended by Stieglitz in New York and Europe.
      Housed in Parts 1 and 2 (2 boxes)
      - Part 1 (Box 108a)
      - Part 2 (Box 108b)
    - Scrapbook Number 8, 1888-1902 (Box 109 (Oversize))
      Contains cast lists cut from programs of opera and theater performances attended by Stieglitz in New York, England and Europe.
  - CLIPPINGS FILES
    The subseries is divided into two sections: Clippings about Alfred Stieglitz and his Work and Clippings about the Stieglitz Circle.
    - Clippings about Alfred Stieglitz and his Work
      - General clippings, 1888-1950, n.d. (Box 110, Folder 2212-2225)
      - America and Alfred Stieglitz, 1934-35 (Box 111, Folder 2226)
      - An American Place, 1950 Nov 26 (Box 111, Folder 2227)
      - Book reviews, 1961-79 (Box 111, Folder 2228)
      - Camera Club of New York, 1901, 1971 (Box 111, Folder 2229)
      - Camera Notes, 1899-1903 (Box 111, Folder 2230)
      - Camera Work, 1902-23 (Box 111, Folder 2231)
      - Exhibitions, 1955-78 (Box 111, Folder 2232)
      - MSS, 1922-24 (Box 111, Folder 2233)
      - Miscellaneous clippings, 1962-71 (Box 111, Folder 2234)
      - Miscellaneous ephemera, 1944-78, n.d. (Box 111, Folder 2235)
      - Sales of Stieglitz's work, 1976, 1980 (Box 111, Folder 2236)
      - Stieglitz Archive, Yale University Library, 1951 Apr (Box 111, Folder 2237)
      - Stieglitz Circle exhibition, Taft Museum, Cincinnati, 1951 (Box 111, Folder 2238)
      - Stieglitz Collection, Art Institute of Chicago, 1949 (Box 111, Folder 2239)
      - Stieglitz Collection, Fisk University, 1949-50 (Box 111, Folder 2240)
      - Stieglitz Collection, Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1949-67 (Box 111, Folder 2241)
      - Stieglitz Collection, miscellaneous, 1949 (Box 111, Folder 2242)
      - Stieglitz Memorial Exhibition, Art Institute of Chicago, 1948-51 (Box 111, Folder 2243)
      - Stieglitz Memorial Exhibition, Museum of Modern Art, 1947 (Box 111, Folder 2244)
      - Stieglitz Memorial Portfolio (Twice a Year Press), 1947-48 (Box 111, Folder 2245)
      - "291" Gallery, 1914-15 (Box 111, Folder 2246)
    - Clippings about the Stieglitz Circle
      - Adams, Ansel, 1930, 1934 (Box 111, Folder 2247)
      - African Negro Art, 1915-36 (Box 111, Folder 2248)
      - Albright Art Gallery, 1910-11 (Box 111, Folder 2249)
      - Alexander, John White, 1914, n.d. (Box 111, Folder 2250)
      - American Amateur Photographer (issue), 1904 Dec (Box 111, Folder 2251)
      - Ames, Charles H., 1892 (Box 111, Folder 2252)
      - Anderson, Sherwood, 1922-41, 1970 (Box 111, Folder 2253)
      - Armory Show, 1913-63 (Box 111, Folder 2254)
      - Bacon, Peggy, 1923, 1928 (Box 111, Folder 2255)
      - Benton, Thomas Hart, 1933-35, n.d. (Box 111, Folder 2256)
      - Bloch, Ernest, 1925-26 (Box 111, Folder 2257)
      - Bluemner, Oscar, 1928 Mar 10 (Box 111, Folder 2258)
      - Bragdon, Claude, 1939 (Box 111, Folder 2259)
      - Brancusi, Constantin, 1914, 1926 (Box 111, Folder 2260)
      - Brigman, Anne, 1971 Mar 27 (Box 111, Folder 2261)
      - Brotherhood of the Linked Ring, 1900-09, n.d. (Box 111, Folder 2262)
      - Bruehl, Anton, 1938 Jan (Box 111, Folder 2263)
      - Bruguière, Francis Joseph, 1927 Apr 3 (Box 111, Folder 2264)
      - Bruno, Guido, 1915 Feb 5 (Box 111, Folder 2265)
      - Carles, Arthur B., 1912 (Box 112, Folder 2266)
      - Cézanne, Paul, 1911-52 (Box 112, Folder 2267)
      - Children's paintings, 1935 Nov 10 (Box 112, Folder 2268)
      - Coburn, Alvin Langdon, 1907-62 (Box 112, Folder 2269)
      - Coomaraswamy, Ananda Kentish, 1924 Feb 16 (Box 112, Folder 2270)
      - Copland, Aaron (Box 112, Folder 2271)
      - Cortissoz, Royal, 1913, 1935 (Box 112, Folder 2272)
      - Craig, Gordon, 1910-31 (Box 112, Folder 2273)
      - Craven, Thomas, 1924-45 (Box 112, Folder 2274)
      - Cromwell, Georgia Engelhard, 1931, 1933 (Box 112, Folder 2275)
      - Cummings, E. E. (Edward Estlin), 1941 Feb 16 (Box 112, Folder 2276)
      - Dada, 1921, n.d. (Box 112, Folder 2277)
      - Davies, Arthur B. (Arthur Bowen), 1926, 1929 (Box 112, Folder 2278)
      - De Casseres, Benjamin, 1912, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 2279)
      - Demachy, Robert, 1906 Jan 11 (Box 112, Folder 2280)
      - De Meyer, Adolf, Baron, 1917 Nov (Box 112, Folder 2281)
      - Demuth, Charles, 1923-71 (Box 112, Folder 2282-2283)
      - de Zayas, Marius
        - [EMPTY FOLDER] (Box 112, Folder 2284)
          See: Zayas, Marius de, Box 114, folder 2393a
      - Dove, Arthur Garfield, 1912-67, n.d. (Box 112, Folder 2285-2286)
      - Dove, Arthur Garfield, n.d. (Box 112, Folder 2286a)
      - Dreier, Katherine Sophie, 1924, 1927 (Box 112, Folder 2287)
      - Eilshemius, Louis M. (Louis Michel), 1932, n.d. (Box 112, Folder 2288)
      - Enters, Angna, 1934-46 (Box 112, Folder 2289)
      - Eugene, Frank, n.d. (Box 112, Folder 2290)
      - Exhibitions - Chicago, 1900-03 (Box 112, Folder 2291)
      - Exhibitions - Glasgow, 1901 (Box 112, Folder 2292)
      - Exhibitions - London, 1901-10 (Box 112, Folder 2293)
      - Exhibitions - Paris, 1901 Oct (Box 112, Folder 2294)
      - Exhibitions - Philadelphia, 1900-01, n.d. (Box 112, Folder 2295)
      - Exhibitions - St. Louis
        See: Louisiana Purchase Exposition, Box 113, folder 2331
      - Expressionism, 1937 Feb (Box 112, Folder 2296)
      - Field, Hamilton Easter, 1921, 1923 (Box 112, Folder 2297)
      - Flint, Ralph, 1932 Nov 5 (Box 112, Folder 2298)
      - Frank, Margaret Naumberg, 1944-45 (Box 112, Folder 2299)
      - Frank, Waldo David, 1921-38, n.d. (Box 112, Folder 2300)
      - Freund, Robert
      - Fry, Roger Eliot, 1943 Jan 23 (Box 112, Folder 2301)
      - Gág, Wanda, 1927 Jun 22 (Box 112, Folder 2302)
      - Gallatin, A. E. (Albert Eugene), 1923 Apr 9 (Box 112, Folder 2303)
      - Genthe, Arnold, 1936 Nov 21 (Box 112, Folder 2304)
      - Grosz, George, 1931-44, n.d. (Box 112, Folder 2305)
      - Gumpert, Martin, 1937 Jul 30 (Box 112, Folder 2306)
      - Halpert, Samuel, 1912, 1962 (Box 112, Folder 2307)
      - Hapgood, Hutchins, 1912-13, n.d. (Box 112, Folder 2308)
      - Hartley, Marsden, 1917-52 (Box 112, Folder 2309-2310)
      - Hartmann, Sadakichi, 1900-16 (Box 112, Folder 2311)
      - Hill, David Octavius, 1931-58 (Box 112, Folder 2312)
      - Hine, Lewis Wickes, 1939 Feb (Box 112, Folder 2313)
      - Hinton, A. Horsley (Alfred Horsley), 1907 Sep 24 (Box 112, Folder 2314)
      - Howald, Ferdinand, 1931 Jan (Box 112, Folder 2315)
      - Impressionism and Post-Impressionism, 1900-11 (Box 112, Folder 2316)
      - James, Rebecca Salsbury, 1933 Dec 17 (Box 112, Folder 2317)
      - Jewell, Edward Alden, 1934, 1947 (Box 112, Folder 2318)
      - Julien Levy Gallery
      - Kahler, Erich, [1945?] (Box 113, Folder 2319)
      - Kasebier, Gertrude, 1907 Apr (Box 113, Folder 2320)
      - Katz, Leo, 1937-43 (Box 113, Folder 2321)
      - Keiley, Joseph, 1943 Jun (Box 113, Folder 2322)
      - Kopman, Benjamin, n.d. (Box 113, Folder 2323)
      - Kreymborg, Alfred, 1925 Mar 29 (Box 113, Folder 2324)
      - Kuhn, Walt, 1913 Feb 6 (Box 113, Folder 2325)
      - Kuniyoshi, Yasuo, 1940, 1942 (Box 113, Folder 2326)
      - Lachaise, Gaston, 1927-35 (Box 113, Folder 2327)
      - Lawrence, D. H. (David Herbert), 1926-31 (Box 113, Folder 2328)
      - Lewis, John L., 1940 Nov 1 (Box 113, Folder 2329)
      - London Secession, 1911 May 16 (Box 113, Folder 2330)
      - Louisiana Purchase Exposition, 1904 Apr 30 (Box 113, Folder 2331)
      - Loy, Mina, n.d. (Box 113, Folder 2332)
      - Luhan, Mabel Dodge, 1914-36, n.d. (Box 113, Folder 2333)
      - McBride, Henry, 1921-49, n.d. (Box 113, Folder 2334)
      - Macdonald-Wright, Stanton, 1916-43 (Box 113, Folder 2335)
      - Marin, John, 1911-73, n.d. (Box 113, Folder 2336-44)
      - Matisse, Henri, 1910-36, n.d. (Box 113, Folder 2345)
      - Maurer, Alfred, 1924-49 (Box 113, Folder 2346)
      - Mellquist, Jerome, 1942 (Box 113, Folder 2347)
      - Miller, Henry, 1945 Dec 28 (Box 114, Folder 2348)
      - Mumford, Lewis, 1927-43 (Box 114, Folder 2349)
      - Newhall, Beaumont and Nancy Wynne, 1937-42 (Box 114, Folder 2350)
      - Norman, Dorothy, 1939, 1948 (Box 114, Folder 2351)
      - Ornstein, Leo, n.d. (Box 114, Folder 2352)
      - Pascin, Jules, 1924 Jan 13 (Box 114, Folder 2353)
      - Philadelphia Photographic Society, 1902, 1910 (Box 114, Folder 2354)
      - Phillips, Joseph, 1940 Apr 20 (Box 114, Folder 2355)
      - Phillips Memorial Gallery, 1941-45 (Box 114, Folder 2356)
      - Photography, 1904-53, n.d. (Box 114, Folder 2357)
      - Photo-Secession, 1904, 1962 (Box 114, Folder 2358)
      - Picabia, Francis, 1913-28 (Box 114, Folder 2359)
      - Picasso, Pablo, 1910-67 (Box 114, Folder 2360)
      - Pinson, Koppel S. (Koppel Shub), 1944 (Box 114, Folder 2361)
      - Pollitzer, Anita, 1975 (Box 114, Folder 2362)
      - Porter, Eliot, 1940 (Box 114, Folder 2363)
      - Powell, John, 1925 Jun 22 (Box 114, Folder 2364)
      - Puma, Fernando, 1943 Nov 4 (Box 114, Folder 2365)
      - Quinn, John, 1926 Jan 1 (Box 114, Folder 2366)
      - Rainer, Luise, 1937 May 29 (Box 114, Folder 2367)
      - Ray, Man, 1915 Nov 14 (Box 114, Folder 2368)
      - Reinhardt, Max
        See: Oversize, Box 246, Folder 4340
      - Rodin, Auguste, 1917-46, n.d. (Box 114, Folder 2369)
      - Rönnebeck, Arnold, 1925-45 (Box 114, Folder 2370)
      - Rosenfeld, Paul, 1921-46, n.d. (Box 114, Folder 2371)
      - Rubin, Reuven, 1951 Mar 4 (Box 114, Folder 2372)
      - Rugg, Harold, 1941-42 (Box 114, Folder 2373)
      - Sandburg, Carl, 1923 Jan 21 (Box 114, Folder 2374)
      - Seldes, Gilbert, 1928 Feb (Box 114, Folder 2375)
      - Severini, Gino, 1917 Mar (Box 114, Folder 2376)
      - Shaw, George Bernard, 1895-1945 (Box 114, Folder 2377)
      - Sloan, John, 1928, 1939 (Box 114, Folder 2378)
      - Smith, Pamela Colman, 1979 (Box 114, Folder 2379)
      - Steichen, Edward, 1908-78, n.d. (Box 114, Folder 2380)
      - Stein, Gertrude and Leo, 1912-41, n.d. (Box 114, Folder 2381)
      - Stettheimer, Florine, 1945, 1951 (Box 114, Folder 2382)
      - Strand, Paul, 1921-76 (Box 114, Folder 2383)
      - Todd, F. Dundas (Frederick Dundas), 1902 Mar (Box 114, Folder 2384)
      - Toomer, Jean, 1929 May 25 (Box 114, Folder 2385)
      - Varèse, Edgard, 1940 Dec 13 (Box 114, Folder 2386)
      - Villany, Adorée, 1912 Mar 9 (Box 114, Folder 2387)
      - Walkowitz, Abraham, 1917, 1945 (Box 114, Folder 2388)
      - Ward, H. Snowden (Henry Snowden), 1908 Oct 6 (Box 114, Folder 2389)
      - Weber, Max, 1910, n.d. (Box 114, Folder 2390)
      - White, Clarence H., 1938 Oct (Box 114, Folder 2391)
      - Wright, Cedric, 1946 Jan (Box 114, Folder 2392)
      - Wright, Frank Lloyd, 1939 Jan (Box 114, Folder 2393)
      - Zayas, Marius de, 1909-16 (Box 114, Folder 2393a)
      - Zorach, William, 1935 Apr (Box 114, Folder 2394)
      - Miscellaneous and unidentified, 1906-46, n.d. (Box 114, Folder 2395)
  - CLIPPING BOARDS
    The subseries contains sheets of pulpboard onto which entire newspaper pages and assorted clippings were dry mounted in random order. See Appendix Two of this finding aid for an expanded description of the clipping boards' contents.
    - Portfolio One: Sheets 1-25, 1908-34 (Box 115 (Oversize))
    - Portfolio Two: Sheets 26-56, 1908-36, n.d. (Box 116 (Oversize))
  - PUBLICATIONS OF STIEGLITZ'S GALLERIES
    General note
    Consult Orbis, the library's online catalog, for additional copies of exhibition-related publications.
    - Little Galleries of the Photo-Secession/"291" Gallery
      - Announcements, exhibition checklists, etc., 1905-17 (Box 117, Folder 2396)
        Bound volume containing a list of Photo-Secession members, and copies of exhibition calendars, checklists, announcements and statements issued through April 1917.
      - O'Keeffe exhibition announcement, 1917 Apr (Box 117, Folder 2397)
    - Anderson Galleries - Room 303
      - Forum Exhibition of Modern American Painters, 1916 (Box 118, Folder 2398)
      - Announcements and exhibition checklists, 1921-25 (Box 118, Folder 2399)
      - "Seven Americans", 1925 (Box 118, Folder 2400)
      - Hartley auction, 1921 (Box 118, Folder 2401)
    - Intimate Gallery
      - Announcements and exhibition checklists, 1925-29 (Box 118, Folder 2402-2404)
      - Folders which held announcements, 1927, 1929 (Box 118, Folder 2405)
      - Phillips letter, 1927 (Box 118, Folder 2406)
    - An American Place
      - Announcements and exhibition checklists, 1930-46 (Box 118, Folder 2407-2414)
      - John Marin letters, 1931-41 (Box 118, Folder 2415)
      - "It Must Be Said," nos. 1-4, 7, 1932-37 (Box 118, Folder 2416)
        Contain essays by Herbert Seligmann, Cary Ross, Evelyn Howard and Ralph Flint.
      - "It Has Been Said," nos. 1-4, 1932-34 (Box 118, Folder 2417)
      - "It Should Be Remembered," no. 1, 1933 Oct (Box 118, Folder 2418)
      - "It Might Be Said," no. 1, 1937 Feb (Box 118, Folder 2419)
    - 291
      - A special collection of issues hand-colored by artists and annotated by Stieglitz, in a custom slipcase. Includes issues with color added by de Zayas, Marin, and Picabia, and photogravure proof of "The Steerage" printed under Stieglitz's supervision. (Box 119)
  - AUTOGRAPH COLLECTION
    - Letters and fragments, affixed to boards
      - Letters and fragments, signatures A-H, 1866-84, n.d. (Box 120, Folder 2420)
        Includes: Adam, Bettelheim, Beust, Billings, Braith, Brandt, Carriere, Frederick (Grand Duke of Baden), Grützner, Hildebrandt (with sketch of San Francisco)
      - Letters and fragments, signatures H-Z, 1856-83, n.d. (Box 120, Folder 2421)
        Includes: Prinz Hohenlohe, Cardinal v. Hohenlohe, Junkermann, Kauffmann, Kendell, Kindermann, Lewinsky, Schwanenthaler, Waddington, Wrangel, and a petition with eighteen signatures including those of Richter, Schmidt, Bendemann
      - Fragments from documents signed by Karl August, Amelie, E. A. Constantine, and Ernst August, all of Weimar, 1728-1878 (Box 120, Folder 2422)
      - Drawing and autograph note by Schinkel; autograph note by Schadow, 1830, 1846, n.d. (Box 120, Folder 2423)
      - Letters and fragments, signatures unidentified, 1796-1884, n.d. (Box 120, Folder 2424)
    - Letters and fragments, loose
      - Letters and fragments, signatures A-E, 1830-84, n.d. (Box 120, Folder 2425)
        Includes: Achenbach, Alma-Tadema, Arnim, Begas, Bernays, Carolus-Duran, Carriere, Catalani, Defregger, Dill, Döring, Eckermann
      - Letters and fragments, signatures F-H, 1789-1884, n.d. (Box 120, Folder 2426)
        Includes: Garfield, Gauss, Giesebrecht, Gleichen (Schiller), Gleim, Götze, Grimminger, Grün, Grützner, Hahn, Hanslick, Hauk, Hoff
      - Letters and fragments, signatures I-L, 1818-84, n.d. (Box 120, Folder 2427)
        Includes: Immermann, Joachim, Jutz, Kinkel, Kirinoff, Knaus, Kobell, L'Arronge, Lassalle, Lepsius, Leschetizky, Lewald, Liebig, Loewe, Lucca
      - Letters and fragments, signatures M-P, 1775-1886, n.d. (Box 120, Folder 2428)
        Includes: Merck, Meissonier, Müller, Munkacsy, Oberlander, Passini, Pettenkofer, Piloty, Polko, Preller, Princess Victoria, Proska
      - Letters and fragments, signatures R-S, 1783-1883, n.d. (Box 120, Folder 2429)
        Includes: Rettig, Reuter, Roquette, Rosenthal, Sacher-Masoch, Saphir, Schack, Schaper, Scherr, Schliemann, Schott, Schleich, Schlosser
      - Letters and fragments, signatures S-Z, 1869-84, n.d. (Box 120, Folder 2430)
        Includes: Schwind, Siemering, Stichling/von Gerden, Stoecker, Thumann, Treitschke, Victor Emanuel of Savoy, Queen Victoria, Werner, Wildenbruch, Wolff, Zola
      - Letters and documents, signatures unidentified, 1780-1884, n.d. (Box 120, Folder 2431)
    - Autograph collection folders
      - Folders which formerly held autographs, inscribed by Stieglitz, n.d.
    - Bound volumes
      - Juvenile autograph album, 1874-79 (Box 120, Folder 2432)
        Homemade album of ruled paper containing autographed scraps pasted in, signed by Stieglitz family members and friends; also two loose sheets of signatures.
      - Juvenile autograph album, 1876-79 (Box 120, Folder 2433)
        Bound album containing signatures of Stieglitz's friends from grammar school, including Frank ("Sime") Hermann and Albert Strauss.
        [Gift of Sue Davidson Lowe, 1978]
      - Erkenne Dich Selbst!, 1884-1917 (Box 120, Folder 2434)
        Bound volume of questionnaires designed to acquaint one with one's friends. Includes entries by Alfred Stieglitz, his parents, siblings, aunt and daughter, as well as friends Hasemann, Encke, Krummel and Schubart among others.
      - Ghosts of My Friends, 1911-13 (Box 120, Folder 2435)
        Bound volume containing signatures of Katherine Stieglitz's family and friends, folded over when the ink was still wet to make blot images.
- Photographs, Series IV; 16.8; (31 boxes)
  The series in arranged in six subseries: Photographs by Alfred Stieglitz; Photographs of Alfred Stieglitz; Photographs of Family and Friends; Collections of Personal and Study Photographs; Photographs by Stieglitz's Associates, and Exhibition Installation Photographs.
  Box 146: for research use only. May not be duplicated.
  - PHOTOGRAPHS BY ALFRED STIEGLITZ
    The subseries is arranged in four sections: Paper Prints; Photogravures; Autochromes; and Lantern Slides. See also study prints by Stieglitz in Boxes 143-44; 146-48, and Georgia O'Keeffe's "Waste Basket Collection."
    - Paper Prints
      - Equivalent, [1925] (Box 121, Folder 2436)
      - Equivalent, [1925] (Box 121, Folder 2437)
      - Equivalent, [1926] (Box 121, Folder 2438)
      - Equivalent, [1926?] (Box 121, Folder 2439)
      - Equivalent, [1927] (Box 121, Folder 2440)
      - Equivalent, [1927] (Box 121, Folder 2441)
      - Equivalent, [1929] (Box 121, Folder 2442)
      - Equivalent, [1930] (Box 121, Folder 2443)
      - Equivalent, [1931] (Box 121, Folder 2444)
      - Equivalent, [1935?] (Box 121, Folder 2445)
      - Equivalent, n.d. (Box 121, Folder 2446)
      - Equivalent, n.d. (Box 121, Folder 2447)
      - "The Hand of Man", [1902] (Box 122, Folder 2448)
      - [Coenties Slip, Manhattan], ca. 1902 (Box 122, Folder 2449)
      - "Lower Manhattan", [1910] (Box 122, Folder 2450)
      - Georgia O'Keeffe [hands], [1918] (Box 122, Folder 2451)
      - Georgia O'Keeffe [clutching collar], [1918] (Box 122, Folder 2452)
      - O'Keeffe and Davidson pruning in orchard, [1920] (Box 122, Folder 2453)
      - Georgia O'Keeffe, [1923] (Box 122, Folder 2454)
      - Bly [gardener, Lake George], n.d. (Box 122, Folder 2455)
      - Lake George [farmhouse], 1925 (Box 122, Folder 2456)
      - Lake George [farmhouse with tree, reversed print], 1931 (Box 122, Folder 2457)
      - Lake George [side of farmhouse], n.d. (Box 122, Folder 2458)
      - Lake George [outbuilding], n.d. (Box 122, Folder 2459)
      - Lake George [outbuilding with bed], n.d. (Box 122, Folder 2460)
      - "The Jungfrau Group", [1894] (Box 123, Folder 2461)
      - "The Letter Box", [1894] (Box 123, Folder 2462)
      - "My Father" [Edward Stieglitz], [1891] (Box 123, Folder 2463)
      - "Ma" [Hedwig Stieglitz], [1914] (Box 123, Folder 2464)
      - Georgia O'Keeffe, [1919] (Box 123, Folder 2465)
      - Georgia O'Keeffe [hands and thimble], [1920] (Box 123, Folder 2466)
      - Dorothy Obermeyer Schubart, n.d. (Box 123, Folder 2467)
        Gift of Dorothy O. Schubart, 1954
      - William H. Schubart, n.d. (Box 123, Folder 2468)
      - Sherwood Anderson, [1923] (Box 124, Folder 2469)
      - Marie Rapp Boursault, [1915] (Box 124, Folder 2470)
      - Marcel Duchamp, [1923] (Box 124, Folder 2471-2472)
      - Waldo Frank, [1922] (Box 124, Folder 2473)
      - Marsden Hartley, [1911] (Box 124, Folder 2474)
      - Marsden Hartley, n.d. (Box 124, Folder 2475-2476)
      - Paul Haviland, [1913] (Box 124, Folder 2477)
      - Joseph Keiley, [1907?] (Box 124, Folder 2478)
      - Paul Rosenfeld, [1923?] (Box 124, Folder 2479)
      - Paul Rosenfeld, n.d. (Box 124, Folder 2480)
      - Dorothy True, n.d. (Box 124, Folder 2481)
      - New York [from the Shelton], [1930] (Box 125, Folder 2482)
      - New York [from the Shelton], [1930] (Box 125, Folder 2483)
      - New York [from the Shelton], [1930] (Box 125, Folder 2484)
      - Lake George [farmhouse], [1932] (Box 125, Folder 2485)
      - Lake George [farmhouse window], [1934] (Box 125, Folder 2486)
      - Lake George [outbuilding], [1934?] (Box 125, Folder 2487)
      - Lake George [outbuilding, detail], [1934] (Box 125, Folder 2488)
      - Lake George [outbuilding, winter], [1923] (Box 125, Folder 2489)
      - Lake George [view to the lake], [1931] (Box 125, Folder 2490)
      - Lake George [view to the lake], [1932] (Box 125, Folder 2491)
      - Lake George [view to the lake], n.d. (Box 125, Folder 2492)
      - "The Village Philosopher" (in original frame), 1894 (Box 126, Folder 2493)
        Gift of Mr. and Mrs. Duncan Somerville, 1981
      - "Weary" (in original frame), 1890 (Box 126, Folder 2494)
    - Photogravures
      - Volume Number 1: small format prints, 1897-1913 (Box 127)
        See Appendix Three for full listing of images in this volume.
      - Volume Number 2: large format prints, 1892-1913 (Box 128)
      - "The City of Ambition", [1910] (Box 129, Folder 2495)
      - "Excavating - New York", n.d. (Box 129, Folder 2496)
      - "The Flat-iron", n.d. (Box 129, Folder 2497)
      - "The Hand of Man", [1902] (Box 129, Folder 2498)
      - "Miss S.R.", 1904 (Box 129, Folder 2499)
      - "The Pool - Deal", n.d. (Box 129, Folder 2500)
      - "The Race Track" [Going to the Start], 1902 (Box 129, Folder 2501)
      - "Spring - The Child", [1901] (Box 129, Folder 2502)
      - "Spring Showers - The Street Cleaner", [1900] (Box 129, Folder 2503)
      - "The Steerage", [1907] (Box 129, Folder 2504)
      - Three Stieglitz Collection labels from previously unframed photogravures, ca. 1914 (Box 129, Folder 2505)
    - Autochromes